coolicool.com 2019-03-06

# Privacy Policy

CooliCool.com is aware that the security of your private information from the use of our website is an important concern. We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. Therefore we would like you to know what data we maintain and what data we discard. With this privacy notice, we would like to inform you about our security measures.

Information Collection and Use Personal Information

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

**• To personalize your experience**  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

**• To improve our website**  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

**• To improve customer service**  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

**• To process transactions**

All transactions are processed by www.coolicool.com

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose

of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

**• To send periodic emails**

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

**OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS**

Upon your request, we will:  
(a) correct or update your personal information;  
(b) stop sending emails to your email address;  
(c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests on our coolicool facebook ([www.facebook.com/CooliCoolFans](https://www.facebook.com/CooliCoolFans)) or email your requests to CooliCool.com's Customer Support Center ([support@coolicool.com](mailto:support@coolicool.com)) Please do not email your credit card number or other sensitive information.
